Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Communications Department records, ca. 1970-2011
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Communications Department records, ca. 1970-2011
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Communications Department records, ca. 1970-2011
24-10-3338
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Communications Department
9.5 cubic ft.
Videocassettes, audio cassettes, press releases, tear sheets, publications, photographs, and ephemera.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Audiovisual materials produced and collected by the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Department of Communications, primarily related to.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Communications Department of the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine is responsible for publicity and external relations for the college.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Videocassettes, audio cassettes, press releases, tear sheets, publications, slides, photographs, and ephemera from the Communications Department of the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine, dating from ca. 1970-2002.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University--College of Veterinary Medicine--Department of Communications
Subjects:
Veterinary Medicine -- Study and teaching.
Form and Genre Terms:
Audiocassettes; Video cassettes; Photographs
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Many of the video cassettes are in formats that require equipment unavailable at the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections. Special arrangements are necessary to view these materials.
See also the Veterinary College of Medicine Biomedical Communications Dept. records, #24-14-3352 and the Veterinary College of Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, #24-4-3385.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Audio and Video Cassettes
Boxes: 1, 7 -11
Several audio and video cassettes of varying formats. Most of the video cassettes are copies of stories run on television news or science programs featuring Cornell veterinarians. Some include local news coverage of college events. The audio tapes include recordings of college events as well as a number of American Association for the Advancement of Science program tapes. There are also 8 video tapes of interviews with several former deans of the college and then-president Hunter Rawlings which were recorded in 2000 for a promotional "Millennium" video that was never completed.
Series II. Publicity Subject Files
Boxes: 2 and 6
Press releases, tear sheets (news clippings), and miscellaneous publications containing references to college people, events and issues.
Series III. Photographs by Subject
Boxes: 2 - 4 and 9
Photographs, mostly from University Photography, arranged by subject; contains some slides.
Series IV. Photographs by Department
Boxes: 5 and 6
Negatives, contact sheets and some photos. Mostly portraits of faculty and staff arranged by department.
Series V. Ephemera
Boxes: 7
2 medallions created for the college centennial in 1994.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Audio and Video Cassettes
  - VHS Video Cassettes
    - Veterinary Medicine in the 1930s, loop tape dubbed from 16mm, March 15, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Veterinary Medicine in 1955 and 1966s, loop tape dubbed from 16mm, March 15, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Veterinary Medicine in the 1970s, loop tape dubbed from 16mm, March 15, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Energy metabolism in the race horse: A research study by Lynn Dunn, 1987 (Box 7)
    - High Speed Treadmill: Kathy Petersson, January 1988 (Box 7)
    - An oral history:1868-1908, as related by Dr. Ellis P. Leonard, Class of 1934 (2 copies), 1990 (Box 7)
    - Dr. Ellis P. Leonard, Karen Redmond, ETV studio, raw footage, Feb. 27, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Babe press conference, Channel 5 Syracuse, May 17, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Babe autopsy news conference, May 17, 1990 (Box 7)
    - WCNY Good Afternoon: J. Saidla, S. Moise, R. Riis, May 24, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Ground Breaking, raw footage, June 9, 1990 (Box 7)
    - WCNY Good Afternoon, June 15, 1990 (Box 7)
    - NBC Closer Look, February 19, 1991 (Box 7)
    - NASA interview re STS-58 mission: Martin Fettman, DVM 1980, 1993 (Box 7)
    - NASA: Martin Fettman Training, dub from betacam, ca. 1990s (Box 7)
    - One Medicine: Drs Bud Tennant, John Cummings and Peter Nathanielz, introduced by Dean Phemister, October 9, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Dr. Kallfely on Good Morning America, February 18, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Unusual Jobs: Ophthalmology, Kern and Neader; Acupuncture, Dill, Channel 3TV, ca. 1987-1993 (Box 7)
    - Equine Motor Neuron Disease, Cornell Media Services, ca. 1987-1993 (Box 7)
    - Flower-Sprecher Library, Renaming Ceremony and Rhodes Scholarship Presentation Ceremony, 1994 (Box 7)
    - President Rhodes' Address at Centennial Luncheon, March 21, 1994 (Box 8)
    - Groundhog Day, Channel 7 (Ithaca) and Channel 12 (Binghamton), Feb. 2, 1996 (Box 8)
    - BSE News Conference, April 10, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Kitten Personality Test: Dr. Katherine Houpt and Dr. Soraya Jarbe-Diaz (2 copies), June 26, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Blood ?: Dr. Alan Dobson, September 11, 1996 (Box 8)
    - The Gentle Doctor 604 and 610 (Arleigh, Mini Ponies), 1996 (Box 8)
    - Cornell Sled Dogs: Dr. Arleigh Reynolds, January 9, 1997 (Box 8)
    - The Gentle Doctor 604 and 610 / Cornell Sled Dogs: Dr. Arleigh Reynolds, 1996, 1997 (Box 8)
    - College of Veterinary Medicine, SCAVMA Tour, February 10, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Dedication Ceremony for Bilinski Laboratory, Veterinary Medical Center, June 7, 1997 (Box 8)
    - UMBRA Wonder Dog: Dr. Arleigh Reynolds / Pet Problems: Dr. Katherine Houpt, WBNG TV (2 copies), November 1997 (Box 8)
    - Pampering Pets, CBS Saturday Morning: Dr. James Richards, November 15, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Cats & Dogs, Science & Technology Special, CNN: W. Miller, J. Richards and J. Scarlett, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Tufts, Veterinary Medicine, NOVA (2 Copies), February 3, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Cats: Dr. Frank, February 24, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Fat Pets, 20/20, ABC, March 2, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Cornering the Killer, Pt 3 of War on Cancer Series, Science Frontiers, The Learning Channel, March 6, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Dog Genome Map, ABC Discovery News, March 1998 (Box 8)
    - Open House, local news coverage re: demonstrators, April 1998 (Box 8)
    - Southside, November 13, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Fundamentals of Draft Horse Shoeing, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Southside Community Center, Healthy Pet Clinic Interviews, January 26, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Healthy Pet Clinic at Southside Community Center, February 2, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Ask the Veterinarian - New York River Otter Project, AHN Cable, March 9, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Vets in Practice, Wildlife Emergency, Emergency Vets, March 14, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Petsburg, USA, Disney's Animal Planet, Episodes 61/62, March 15, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Pet Allergies, CBS Saturday Morning: Dr. Jim Richards, May 15, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Animal Behavior, ABC News: Dr. Vint Virga, August 14, 1999 (Box 8)
    - River Otter Project, Cornell's Wildlife Health Program, CNN Science & Technology: Dr. Barry Hartup, October 5, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Cornell Companions at BOCES, Northeast School, News Center 7, October 29, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Waste Management Project, Vet School EIS, Newscenter 7: Dean Donald Smith, November 8, 2000, November 10, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Helping pets Live Longer, WSTM TV3: Rodney Page and Ann Harris, November 9, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Discovery CA Interview with jon Hill, March, 9, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine, compiled footage, March 12, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Cloning, CNN: Johnathan Hill, March 27, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Companion Animal Medicine, WROC TV8, May 21, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Horse Genome Project, ABC Nightly News: Dr. Douglas Antczak, June 9, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Breed All About It, Animal Planet: Rory Todhunter and Andrea Lee, Class of 2002, July 16, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Horse Genome Project, The Gamble, Science Times, New York Times Television, National Geographic Channel: Dr. Douglas Antczak, November 13, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Lyle Vanclief Address, Agroterrorism & Bio-Security, November 30, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Agroterrorism & Bio-Security: A Forum for Experts from the U.S. & Canada, November 30, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Agroterrorism & Bio-Security, US-Canada Cooperation, The Honorable Lyle W. Vanclief, Minister of Agriculture and Agri-food, Canada, November 30, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Behavior Issues: Dr. Katherine Houpt, ca. 1994-2001 (Box 8)
    - Who Needs Sleep, ca. 1994-2001 (Box 8)
    - Good Dogs Make Good Neighbors, AVMA Video News Release: Dr. Katherine Houpt, ca. 1994-2001 (Box 8)
    - Food for Thought, programme 3, Border Television Video Production, n.d. (Box 7)
    - Unidentified (Box 7)
    - "M. Frongillo" (Department of Microbiology, Immunology and Parasitology) (Box 9)
    - ACUP Acceptance - Alexander deLahunta, December 2002 (Box 9)
    - ABC Dscovery News, Dog Genome Map, Gus Aguirre, March 1998 (Box 10)
    - Norman (dog), Gus Aguirre) (Box 10)
    - Interviews with Deans of the College of Veterinary Medicine as well as Hunter Rawlings for Millennium project., 2000 (Box 9)
  - KCS Video Cassettes
    - Colic: Dr. Hackett and Karen Redmond, ca. 1987-1993 (Box 1)
    - Endoscopy: Dr. Hackett and Karen Redmond, ca. 1987-1993 (Box 1)
    - Endoscopy: Dr. Hackett, ca. 1987-1993 (Box 1)
    - Animal models tape, Walleyes footage only, #2559: Karen Redmond, ca. 1987-1993 (Box 1)
    - "Animal models - Raw footage - #2546", October 1987 (Box 1)
    - Unidentified (Box 1)
  - KCA Video Cassettes
    - People for Ethical Treatment of Animals, Ch. 13 program (2 copies), April 12, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Artificial Dog: Dr. Susan Wade and Dr. Jay Georgi, Dec. 23, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Amie the cat and artificial dogs, fleas through microscope, Oct. 1987 (Box 1)
    - Unidentified (2 cassettes), ca. 1987-1993 (Box 1)
  - KSA Video Cassette
    - In the James Law Tradition: The First 100 Years of the College of Veterinary Medicine at Cornell University, 1993 (Box 1)
  - 3.5" X 6" Beta Video Cassettes
    - Computer Models of Animals, Cornell University News, c/o. Roger Sefelken, ca. 1987-1993 (Box 1)
    - Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine, compiled footage, March 12, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Agroterrorism & Bio-Security: A Forum for Experts from the U.S. & Canada, November 30, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Interviews with Deans of the College of Veterinary Medicine as well as Hunter Rawlings for Millennium project., 2000 (Box 10)
  - DP 121 Digital Video Cassette
    - Discovery CA Feed Tape, Jon Hill, March 9, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Audio Cassettes
    - NYSCVM Commencement, May 30, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Vet School Ceremonies, June 9, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Dr. T.R. Houpt (Side A )/ Babe Necropsy News Conference (Side B), 1990 (Box 7)
    - Veterinary College Centennial Kick-Off, Auditorium Program: Dr. Kallfelz and Dean Phemister, September 4, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Dean Loew with Metta Winter, September 1995 (Box 7)
    - The Environment Show, WAMC, October 17 1998 (Box 7)
    - Penis Research: German Interview with Diane Kelly, December 1999 (Box 7)
    - Intrusive Cats: Why Is It? American Association for the Advancement of Science program, March 1999 (Box 7)
    - Grazing Pets, with Dr. Larry J. Thompson: Why Is It? American Association for the Advancement of Science program, March 1999 (Box 7)
    - Open Air Dogs: Why Is It? American Association for the Advancement of Science program, August 1999 (Box 7)
    - Shaking Dogs: Why Is It? American Association for the Advancement of Science program, September 1999 (Box 7)
    - Cat's Meow: Science Update, American Association for the Advancement of Science program, March 2000 (Box 7)
    - Dog Belly Button: Why Is It? American Association for the Advancement of Science program, February 2001 (Box 7)
    - Cat Andtidepressant: Science Update, American Association for the Advancement of Science program, March 21, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Animal Instincts Radio program, 1994-1997 (Box 11)
- Series II. Publicity Subject Files
  - News Releases and Tear Sheets, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - News Releases and Tear Sheets, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - News Releases and Tear Sheets, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - News Releases and Tear Sheets, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - News Releases and Tear Sheets, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Vet articles- General, 2007-2008 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Vet articles- General, 2007-2008 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Vet articles- General, 2007-2008 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Vet Articles - General, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - General, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - General, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - General, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chronicle Articles, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - In the News, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - University News Press Releases, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Animal Rights Information, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Development, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Education, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Incinerator, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - People, Awards and Honors, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Research, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Service, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Wildlife, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Report of Private Support, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Report of Private Support, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Centennial Celebration Publications, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Rolling Bone, 1996-2002 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Media Inquiries, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Media Inquiries, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Media Inquiries - Gentle Doctor, PBS, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Media Inquiries - Japanese Fuji Network, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Franklin Loew - General, 1972, 1988, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Franklin Loew - Appointment, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Stories
    - General, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - College Named, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Research, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Service, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - College Faculty, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Students, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Alumni, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Curriculum, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Diagnostics Lab - General, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Diagnostics Lab - Mad Cow Disease/BSE, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Veterinary Medical Teaching Hospital, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Cats, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Dogs, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Horses, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Farm Animals, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Wildlife, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Clippings: Aquatic Mammals, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Clippings: Avian, 2003; 2006 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Clippings: Avian Flu, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Clippings: Baboons, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Clippings: Bovines, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Clippings: Canine Attacks, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Clippings: Canine Diet/Pills, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Clippings: Canine Dogswalk, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Clippings: Canine Flu, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Clippings: Canine Genome Mapping Project, 2004; 2006 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Clippings: Canine Heartworm, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Clippings:Canine Small Size Gene, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Clippings: Canines, 2003-2007 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Clippings: Cornell University Publications and Clippings, 2003-2007 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Clippings: Cornell University Veterinary College Awards, 2003-2007 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Clippings: Cornell University Veterinary College, 2003-2007 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Clippings: Cornell University Veterinary College Center for Reproductive Genomics, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Clippings: Cornell University Veterinary College Comparative Cancer Program: Sprecher Institute, 2003; 2007 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Clippings: Cornell University Veterinary College Faculty, 2003-2006 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Clippings: Cornell University Veterinary College MRI, 2004-2006 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Clippings: Cornell University Veterinary College Students, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Clippings: DNA Research, 2003; 2006 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Clippings: Equine: Barbaro/Speed, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Clippings: Equine: Flipped Palates, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Clippings: Equine Genome Project, 2003; 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Clippings: Equine: Herpesvirus, 2004; 2006 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Clippings: Equine: HERDA and HC Research, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Clippings: Equine: Hoof Care, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Clippings: Equines, 2002-2007 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Clippings: Farriers, 1916; 2003-2004,; 2006 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Clippings: Felines, 2003-2007 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Clippings: Fish, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Clippings: Iraq, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Clippings: Kotlikoff Appointed As Dean, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Clippings: Llamas, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Clippings: Local News, 2002-2004; 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Clippings: Mad Cow/Deer Chronic Wasting Disease, 2004; 2006 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Clippings: Medicine: Animals-Humans Research, 2004-2006 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Clippings: Mice, 2003; 2006 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Clippings: Obituaries, 2002-2003; 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Clippings: Pet Cancer Study, 2002; 2007 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Clippings: Pet Food Scandal, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 23-24)
    - Clippings: Pet Health Monitoring, 2004; 2006 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Clippings: Pet Therapy, 2003; 2007 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Clippings: Pigs, 2003; 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Clippings: Rabies, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Clippings: Reptiles/Amphibians, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Clippings: James Richards Obituaries, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Clippings: Shelter Medicine Program, 2003-2005 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Clippings: Sumatran Rhino, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Clippings: Veterinarian News, 2003-2007 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Clippings: Veterinary General, 2003-2007 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Clippings: VHS Fish Disease, 2003-2004; 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Clippings: Wildlife, 2003; 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Clippings: Zoos, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Brochures and other publications, ca. 1993-2007 (Box 14)
- Series III. Photographs by Subject
  - Ambulatory, ca. 1975-1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Anesthesiology, ca. 1975-1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report Photos, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Annual Report Photos, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Autotutorial, ca. 1980s (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Avian Clinic, ca. 1990s (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Baker Institute, ca. 1975-1990 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Biomedical Electronics, ca. 1970s (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Bovine Research Center, ca. 1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Bovine SPF Unit, ca. 1980s (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Buildings, ca. 1975-1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - College Buildings, ca. 1990s (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Veterinary Medical Center, Exteriors, ca. 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Centennial, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Clinics, ca. 1975-1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Clinic Articles, ca. 1980s (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Community Practices - Slides, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Companion Animal Hospital, ca. 1980s (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Computers, ca. 1975-1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Computing, ca. 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Construction, ca. 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Continuing Education, ca. 1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Diagnostic Lab and Preventative Medicine, ca. 1975-1985, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Equine Performance Test Clinic, ca. 1980s (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Equine Performance Tread Mill, ca. 1975-1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Older and Overused [Equine] Photos, ca. 1970s (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Older and Overused [Equine] Photos, ca. 1970s (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Explorations Course, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Farriery, ca. 1970s (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Feline Health Center, ca. 1975-1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - India, ca. 1970s (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Lab and Technical, ca. 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Lab and Technical, ca. 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Large Animal Isolation, ca. 1980s (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Large Animal Clinic, ca. 1975-1995 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Lasers, ca. 1990s (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Library, ca. 1980s (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Mastitis Control, ca. 1970s (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Medical Records, ca. 1980s (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Modular Resource Center, ca. 1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Open House, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Open House, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Open House - snaps, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Open House, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Open House - negs, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Open House, ca. 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Open House, ca. 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Open House - slides, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Ophthalmology, ca. 1975-1990 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Patients and procedure in VM Teaching Hospital - Wildlife Patients and Exotic Animals, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Patients and procedure in VM Teaching Hospital - Ophthalmology in VMTH, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Patients and procedure in VM Teaching Hospital - Dogs, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Patients and procedure in VM Teaching Hospital - Cats, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Patients and procedure in VM Teaching Hospital - Equine Surgery, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Patients and procedure in VM Teaching Hospital - Farm Animals, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Patients and procedure in VMTeaching Hospital - Horses, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Patients and procedure in VM Teaching Hospital - General Surgery, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Pharmacology, ca. 1980s (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Pharmacy, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Physiology, ca. 1970s (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Pregnancy Lab Utrasound, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Rabies Clinic, ca. 1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Radiology, ca. 1975-1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Reed Farm, ca. 1980s (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Russian Visitors, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Senior Home Visit, ca. 1980s (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Small Animal Clinic, ca. 1975-1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Students - Tutorials, ca. 1980s (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Students of Color, ca. 1974-1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Students at Microscopes, ca. 1974-1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Students - Labs, ca. 1974-1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Students - General, ca. 1980s (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Students in Clinics, ca. 1975-1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Students in Anatomy Labs, ca. 1974-1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Classrooms/Students, ca. 1980s (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Residents - Large Animal Clinic, ca. 1990s (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Residents - Small Animal Clinic, ca. 1990s (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Small Animal Surgery, ca. 1975-1990 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Junior Surgery, ca. 1978-1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Surgery, ca. 1974-1990 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Steffen Food Animal Surgery Sketch by K.L. Berber, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Large Animal Surgery, ca. 1974-1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Terrier Day, ca. 1980s (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Veterinary Circle, ca. 1980s (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Wiswall Learning Lab/Veterinary Education Center, ca. 1990s (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous, ca. 1975-1990 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Slides of various campus buildings, etc., n.d. (Box 9)
- Series IV. Photographs by Department
  - 001 Administration, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 002 Anatomy, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 003 AAAM, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 004 Diagnostic Lab, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 005 Microbiology, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 006 Baker Institute, ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 007 Pathology (folder 1), ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 007 Pathology (folder 2), ca. 1983-1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)